

for work samples, visit

http://www.tyreepini.com

Contact Me

typini@gmail.com (480) 521-0563

## Summary

Data Center Technician with four years combined educational and professional experience utilizing object-oriented programming languages seeking career advancement in **front-end**, **back-end**, **and/or full-stack web development** roles. An adaptable, multifaceted leader who drives innovation through creative problem solving and team collaboration.

# Professional Experience

#### Data Center Technician Chandler AZ

August 2017 - Present

Oracle Corporation

Demonstrates teamwork through ongoing collaboration with Oracle Cloud Infrastructure's Knowledge Management Team analyzing company needs and assessing documentation platforms

Developed a standard operating procedures single-page web application using JavaScript, Bootstrap, ¡Query, and AJAX

Programmed an Auto-Ticket Generator in Node.js to makes chrono calls to Atlassian/JIRA API which increased the audit completion rate to 100%

# High School Teacher Juneau, AK

August 2009 - May 2016

Juneau School District

Music Technology Specialist in Alaska Region V

Built and administered a Linux Ubuntu web server for students and parents to access class related content

Developed a 21-tab Google Sheet Application that coordinated performance schedules, rehearsals, venues, and housing for 11 schools and over 850+ participants in the annual Southeast Alaska Regional Music Festival

Taught required and elective classes, which included teaching Intro to C++

#### **Webmaster** Juneau, AK

November 2015 - December 2016

The Alaska Chapter of American String Teacher's Association Maintained the organization's website hosted by Squarespace

Performed a site overhaul in November 2015

# Web Development Intern Scottsdale, AZ

March 2016

Spark Engine

Assisted CTO with developing and debugging of the company's website

Programmed with Eclipse using JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, and CSS

#### Education

#### DeVry University Chicago, IL

September 2013 - April 2017

Bachelor of Science: Web Development and Administration, 4.0 GPA National Society of Leadership and Success Member

## University of Nevada, Las Vegas Las Vegas, NV August 2006 - August 2009

Master of Education: Curriculum and Instruction, 3.97 GPA Graduate Assistantship as Assistant Residential Life Coordinator

# **Brigham Young University** Provo, UT

September 1998 - August 2005

Bachelor of Arts: Media Arts Studies and Music Composition, 3.74 GPA Sterling Scholar and Heritage Scholarship Award

### Skills

HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript
SQL
C++
Java
C#
ASP.NET
jQuery
JSON
SASS
Node.js
React
Angular JS
Python

npm Webpack

RESTfúl API

AWS Microsoft Visual Studio Dreamweaver Eclipse NetBeans

> Windows OS Mac OS Linux OS

SDLC BEM Unit Testing Debugging Waterfall Agile Scrum Kanban Jira Trello Git

### Certifications

Oracle Linux Advocate April 2018

Certified Data Center Technician April 2019

Career Foundry Full-Stack Immersion Boot Camp In-Progress